A Guide to the William Garber Photograph Collection, 1930-1960
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Broadway (High) School, group of young men and women eating in the cafeteria.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0210; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway (High) School, group of young men and women eating in the cafeteria.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0211; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway School, large group of boys and girls eating in the cafeteria.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0212; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway School, group of young boys and girls eating in the cafeteria.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0213; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway High School, the cafeteria workers in the kitchen.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0214; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway School, three cafeteria workers standing next to a man in a suit.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0215; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway (High) School, the band set up for performance in the gym.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0216; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0216.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0216a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0216.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0216b; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0216.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0216c; 4x5
- Broadway (High) School, women’s basketball team posing in front of the school.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0217; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0217.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0217a; 4x5
- Broadway (High) School, women’s basketball team posing in the gym.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0218; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway (High) School, women’s basketball team posing in the gym.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0219; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway (High) School, three cheerleaders practicing a routine in the grass. Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0220; 4x5
- Broadway (High) School, three cheerleaders mid-jump as they practice a routine outside.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0221; 4x5
- Broadway (High) School, men’s basketball team posing in front of the school. Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0222; 4x5
- Broadway School, a large group of boys and girls in a circular formation, presumably practicing a dance.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0223; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway School, three women and a young girl conversing in some sort of kitchen or storage area.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0224; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway School, three young children in Halloween costumes.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0225; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway (High) School, four young men and women posing next to the school plague.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0226; 4x5
- Broadway (High) School, a young man and woman posing outside.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0227; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0227.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0227a; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway (High) School, four young men and women standing outside.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0228; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0228.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0228a; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway (High) School, four young women sitting a table studying.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0229; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway (High) School, three young women and one young man posing outside.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0230; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway (High) School, four young men and women standing outside.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0231; 4x5
- Broadway (High) School, group of young men and boys wearing Safety Patrol belts, with a school bus in the background.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0232; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway (High) School, a large group of young men/boys outside of the school.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0233; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0233.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0233a; 4x5
- Broadway (High) School, a large group of young men and women outside of the school.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0234; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0234.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0234a; 4x5
- Broadway (High) School, a large group of young men and women outside of the school.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0235; 4x5
- Broadway (High) School, a large group of young men and women outside of the school.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0236; 4x5
- Broadway (High) School, a large group of young men and women outside of the school.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0237; 4x5
- Broadway (High) School, a group of young men and women standing on the front steps.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0238; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0238.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0238a; 2.5x3.5
- Broadway School, a group of boys and girls posing outdoors with their teacher.Before 1952, Image: P0002.02.0239; 2.5x3.5
- New Market High School, view from the back of the auditorium, where a woman and a man are playing the violin and piano on stage.Approx. 1939-1959, Image: P0002.02.0240
  Series 5c, “School Photos: New Market High School,” begins.
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0240.Approx. 1939-1959, Image: P0002.02.0240a
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0240.Approx. 1939-1959, Image: P0002.02.0240b
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0240.Approx. 1939-1959, Image: P0002.02.0240c
- Massanutten Military Academy, Woodstock, Va. Men’s basketball team photo, taken in the gym.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0241; 4x5
  Series 5d, “School Photos: Massanutten Military Academy,” begins.
- Massanutten Military Academy, Woodstock, Va. Football team seated outdoors, with three young men in military uniform in the front row.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0242; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0242.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0242a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0242.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0242b; 4x5
- Massanutten Military Academy, Woodstock, Va. Football team seated outdoors.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0243; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0243.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0243a; 4x5
- Massanutten Military Academy, Woodstock, Va. Members of the football team on the field practicing.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0244; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0244.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0244a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0244.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0244b; 4x5
- Massanutten Military Academy, Woodstock, Va. Five football players posing with three men in military uniform. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0245; 4x5
- Massanutten Military Academy, Woodstock, Va. A football player poses on the field with the football.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0246; 4x5
- Massanutten Military Academy, Woodstock, Va. Three football players standing on the edge of a field.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0247; 4x5
- Massanutten Military Academy, Woodstock, Va. A football player posing on the field with the football.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0248; 4x5
- Massanutten Military Academy, Woodstock, Va. A football team sitting outdoors.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0249; 4x5
- Team photo of a men’s baseball team with the letter “E” on their uniforms.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0250; 4x5
  Series 6a, “Sports and Outdoor Recreation: Baseball,” begins.
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0250.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0250a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0250.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0250b; 4x5
- Team photo of a men’s baseball team with the letter “E” on their uniforms. Fence of a baseball field advertising Woodstock businesses in the background. One player in the back row has “Mount Jackson” on the front of his uniform.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0251; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0251.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0251a; 4x5
- Team photo of an African-American baseball team playing for Elkton, Va., baseball field in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0252; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0252.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0252a; 2.5x2.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0252.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0252b; 2.5x2.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0252.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0252c; 4x5
- Team photo of the Front Royal male baseball team (probably Front Royal Cardinals of the Valley Baseball League), taken in front of a baseball field fence which advertises for Woodstock businesses.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0253; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0253.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0253a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0253.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0253b; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0253.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0253c; 2.5x2.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0253.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0253d; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0253e.
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0583.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0253e; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0253d.
- Team photo of the Grottoes Cardinals (probably of the Valley Twin County League or the Rockingham County League), men’s baseball team, in front of the stands of a baseball field. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0254; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0254.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0254a; 4x5
- Team photo of the New Market men’s baseball team, probably the New Market Rebels, taken in front of the stands of a baseball field.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0255; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0255.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0255a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0255.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0255b; 4x5
- Team photo of the New Market (Rebels) men’s baseball team. Baseball field and fans in the stands in the background.1949, Image: P0002.02.0256; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0256.1949, Image: P0002.02.0256a; 4x5
- Team captain of the New Market (Rebels) baseball team shaking hands on the field with the captain of the (Harrisonburg) Turks.After April 1950., Image: P0002.02.0257; 4x5
- Team photo of the New Market Rebels, baseball team, in front of a fence at the game against the (Harrisonburg) Turks.After April 1950., Image: P0002.02.0258; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0258.After April 1950., Image: P0002.02.0258a; 4x5
- Team photo of the baseball team New Market Rebels in front of the fan stands at the game against the (Harrisonburg) Turks.After April 1950., Image: P0002.02.0259; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0259.After April 1950., Image: P0002.02.0259a; 4x5
- Baseball player of the New Market team throwing a ball in a game against the (Harrisonburg) Turks.After April 1950., Image: P0002.02.0260; 4x5
- Team photo of the Quicksburg men’s baseball team (probably of the Valley Twin County or Rockingham County Leagues), the field and fan stands in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0261; 4x5
- Team photo of the Quicksburg men’s baseball team, with the fence of a baseball field advertising Woodstock businesses in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0262; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0262.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0262a; 4x5
- Team photo of the Quicksburg men’s baseball team, with the fence of a baseball field advertising Woodstock businesses in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0263; 4x5
  Negative seems to be double exposed.
- Team photo of the Romney men’s baseball team, taken on the edge of a baseball field.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0264; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0264.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0264a; 4x5
- Team photo of a men’s baseball team that has the letter “S” stitched into their uniforms. Taken against a fence of a baseball field that advertises Woodstock businesses.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0265; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0265.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0265a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0265.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0265b; 4x5
- Team photo of the Shenandoah men’s baseball team, with a baseball field fence advertising Woodstock businesses in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0266; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0266.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0266a; 4x5
- Team photo of the Shenandoah men’s baseball team, with a baseball field fence advertising Woodstock businesses in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0267; 4x5
- Team photo of the Stanley men’s baseball team, with the fan stands in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0268; 4x5
- Team photo of the Stanley men’s baseball team, with the fan stands in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0269; 4x5
- Team photo of the Stanley men’s baseball team, with the fan stands in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0270; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0270.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0270a; 4x5
- Team photo of the men’s baseball team for the Timberville Hatchery, with the letters “GI’s” on their uniforms. Photo taken inside of a home or office; one member is in a wheelchair.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0271; 2.5x3.5
- Team photo of the men’s baseball team for the Timberville Hatchery, with the letters “GI’s” on their uniforms. Photo taken inside of a home or office; one member is in a wheelchair.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0272; 2.5x3.5
- Team photo of the men’s baseball team for the Timberville Hatchery, with the letters “GI’s” on their uniforms. Photo taken inside of a home or office; one member is in a wheelchair.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0273; 2.5x3.5
- Team photo of the men’s baseball team for the Timberville Hatchery, with the letters “GI’s” on their uniforms. Photo taken inside of a home or office; one member is in a wheelchair.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0274; 2.5x3.5
- Team photo of the men’s baseball team for the Timberville Hatchery, with the letters “GI’s” on their uniforms. Photo taken inside of a home or office; one member is in a wheelchair.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0275; 2.5x3.5
- A baseball player of the Timberville Hatchery team posing with a man in a wheelchair and a large trophy.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0276; 2.5x3.5
- A baseball player of the Timberville Hatchery team posing with a man in a wheelchair and a large trophy.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0277; 2.5x3.5
- A baseball player of the Timberville Hatchery team posing with a man in a wheelchair and a large trophy.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0278; 2.5x3.5
- A man in a wheelchair holding a large trophy belonging to the Timberville Hatchery baseball team.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0279; 2.5x3.5
- A man, presumably the coach or owner of the Timberville Hatchery baseball team, sitting at a desk and looking at a large trophy.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0280; 2.5x3.5
- A man, presumably the coach or owner of the Timberville Hatchery baseball team, sitting in a chair holding a large trophy.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0281; 2.5x3.5
- Team photo of the Woodstock (probably Woodstock River Bandits of the Valley League) men’s baseball team, with a baseball field fence in the background advertising Woodstock businesses.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0282; 4x5
- Baseball catcher and batter playing a game.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0283; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0284, 0285, and 0286.
- Baseball catcher and batter playing a game.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0284; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0283, 0285, and 0286.
- Baseball player swinging at a ball.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0285; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0283, 0284, and 0286.
- Three men walking on the edge of a baseball field.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0286; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0283, 0284, and 0285.
- Seven men posing in a gym before or after playing a game of basketball.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0287; 2.5x3.5
  Series 6b, “Sports and Outdoor Recreation: Basketball,” begins.
- A men’s swim team sitting and standing on the edge of an indoor pool.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0288; 2.5x3.5
  Series 6c, “Sports and Outdoor Recreation: Swimming,” begins.
- View of numerous people watching a sporting event, possibly track, in the stands.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0289; 1.25x1.75
  Series 6d, “Sports and Outdoor Recreation: Track and Field,” begins. Housed with 0290, 0291, 0292.
- Runners in the starting position to begin a race around an outdoor track.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0290; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0289, 0291, and 0292.
- Runners racing on an outdoor track, with spectators in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0291; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0289, 0290, and 0292.
- Runners racing on an outdoor track, with spectators in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0292; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0289, 0290, and 0291.
- An athlete high jumping over a crossbar.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0293; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0294, 0295, and 0296.
- An athlete high jumping over a crossbar.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0294; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0293, 0295, and 0296.
- An athlete high jumping over a crossbar.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0295; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0293, 0294, and 0296.
- An athlete high jumping over a crossbar.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0296; 1.25x1.75
  Housed with 0293, 0294, and 0295.
- View of a large number of people on a sports field, taken from an upper story window and from a distance.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0297; 2.5x3.5
  Series 6e, “Sports and Outdoor Recreation: Miscellaneous Field Recreation,” begins.
- View of a large number of people on a sports field, taken from an upper story window and from a distance.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0298; 2.5x3.5
- View of a large number of people on a sports field, taken from an upper story window and from a distance.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0299; 2.5x3.5
- View of a large number of people on a sports field, taken from an upper story window and from a distance.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0300; 2.5x3.5
- View of a large number of people engaged in various activities on a sports field, taken from a distance.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0301; 2.5x3.5
- Group of young women crossing a large sports field.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0302; 2.5x3.5
- Various groups of people crossing a large sports field.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0303; 2.5x3.5
- A group of men walking across a large sports field, followed by a man carrying a ball, possibly a basketball.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0304; 2.5x3.5
- Four men standing behind a long string of fish that is tied to two trees, and a sign that says: “Blair, 18” 1-14 (and) 17.5 1-12; Max, 16.5-1-5.5; Calvin, 18”-1-14; Paul, 18” 2-3.5 (and) 18” 1-15.5. Big Stoney Creek. 1948.”1948, Image: P0002.02.0305; 2.5x3.5
  Series 6f, “Sports and Outdoor Recreation: Fishing and Hunting,” begins.
- Similar to P0002.02.0305, but closer up.1948, Image: P0002.02.0306; 2.5x3.5
- Similar to P0002.02.0305, but without the sign.1948, Image: P0002.02.0307; 2.5x3.5
- The same strung fish as in P0002.02.0305.1948, Image: P0002.02.0308; 2.5x3.5
- Close-up of the larger strung fish, as seen in P0002.02.0305.1948, Image: P0002.02.0309; 2.5x3.5
- A man holding a fish up to a blackboard, upon which is written: “Brook Trout, Length 13”, Weight 15oz, Captured by Paul Myers, 20 April 1948.”20 April 1948, Image: P0002.02.0310; 2.5x3.5
- Five men laying on their stomachs in the grass, with three small baskets and a large number fish on the ground in front of them.1948, Image: P0002.02.0311; 2.5x3.5
- A man and a boy standing in a kitchen with a large string of fish. c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.02.0312; 2.5x3.5
- A man standing outside of a home with his dog and a gun, holding a long rope with a number of birds strung to it.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0313; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0313.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0313a; 2.5x3.5
- Three women standing on a small bridge, one woman is holding a fish roughly half the size of her body.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0314; 2.5x3.5
- A woman standing on a small bridge holding a fish that is roughly half the size of her body.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0315; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.02.0315.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0315a; 2.5x3.5
- Three women fishing from a small bridge, one pulling a rather large fish out of the water.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0316; 2.5x3.5
- Five people, possibly two men and three women, fishing from a small boat in the middle of a lake or pond.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0317; 2.5x3.5
- Three women fishing from a small bridge.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0318; 2.5x3.5
- Two women fishing from a small bridge, one holding a large fish.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0319; 2.5x3.5
- View of a lake, with a man standing on a pier and waving to an individual that is riding on a boat.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0320; 2.5x3.5
- A number of people standing on and fishing from a pier.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.02.0321; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man standing at a microphone and holding a box. Clown in the background.1947, Image: P0002.03.0001; 2.5.x3.5
  Series 7a, “Horses and Horse Events: Timberville Horse Show, 1947,” begins.
- Timberville Horse Show, a man standing at a microphone.1947, Image: P0002.03.0002; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man standing next to a horse.1947, Image: P0002.03.0003; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man standing next to a horse.1947, Image: P0002.03.0004; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man holding a trophy and standing next to his horse, with two finely dressed women standing nearby.1947, Image: P0002.03.0005; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two men posing on their horses, with a woman standing in front of them.1947, Image: P0002.03.0006; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, side view of a man on a horse that has won a ribbon, with two women and a man standing nearby.1947, Image: P0002.03.0007; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man holding a trophy riding a horse with a ribbon. Three women stand nearby, and a man stands at the horse’s head.1947, Image: P0002.03.0008; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man riding a horse with a ribbon and a trophy, facing three women.1947, Image: P0002.03.0009; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man riding a horse with a ribbon; various other riders and individuals nearby.1947, Image: P0002.03.0010; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man riding a horse with a trophy and a ribbon, while three women stand nearby and a man walks into the shot.1947, Image: P0002.03.0011; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two men and woman standing next to a horse, shown from the side.1947, Image: P0002.03.0012; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a woman riding a horse with a ribbon, and three other women standing next to her. 1947, Image: P0002.03.0013; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man riding a horse and holding an envelope, with a woman standing close by.1947, Image: P0002.03.0014; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a woman riding a horse with a ribbon and laughing. A man and a woman approach the horse.1947, Image: P0002.03.0015; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, front view of a woman riding a horse, while a man and woman stand close by.1947, Image: P0002.03.0016; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, front view of a man riding a horse with a ribbon, and a woman standing close by.1947, Image: P0002.03.0017; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man riding a horse with a ribbon, while a woman speaks to the horse.1947, Image: P0002.03.0018; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man posing on a horse with a woman watching from behind.1947, Image: P0002.03.0019; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a woman and a horse performing a trick.1947, Image: P0002.03.0020; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man riding in a horse-drawn carriage.1947, Image: P0002.03.0021; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man riding a horse with spectators in the background.1947, Image: P0002.03.0022; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man riding a horse with spectators in the background.1947, Image: P0002.03.0023; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two women and a girl standing next to a boy on a horse.1947, Image: P0002.03.0024; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a number of riders and their horses mingling with the crowd and posing for the camera.1947, Image: P0002.03.0025; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, two men and women standing on a platform.1947, Image: P0002.03.0026; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, three women sitting on a platform, with two men standing behind them. 1947, Image: P0002.03.0027; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, three women standing on a platform, one holding a trophy.1947, Image: P0002.03.0028; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, front view of a man riding a horse, and another man standing next to him. 1947, Image: P0002.03.0029; 2.5x3.5
- Timberville Horse Show, a man riding a horse.1947, Image: P0002.03.0030; 2.5x3.5
  Negative is extremely faded.
- Timberville Horse Show, a number of individuals standing next to a horse with a wreath of flowers around its neck.1947, Image: P0002.03.0031; 2.5x3.5